https://www.xiris.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Last Modified: April 1, 2020
We at Xiris (Xiris Automation Inc., Xiris Automation GmbH, and Xiris Automation APAC) are committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy applies to the information and data collected by Xiris, including the information collected on our Website (www.xiris.com) or through other channels as described below.
This Privacy Notice describes how we collect, receive, use, store, share, transfer, and process your personal information. It also describes your choices regarding use, as well as your rights of access and correction of your personal information. If you do not agree with the data practices described in this Privacy Policy, you should not use the Website.
We periodically update this Privacy Policy. We will post any privacy policy changes on this page. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy periodically. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our treatment of the information you provide us, please write to us by email at sales@xiris.com or by mail to Xiris Automation Inc., 1016 Sutton Drive, Unit C5, Burlington, Ontario, Canada L7L 6B8. Attn: Privacy.
What Information We Collect About You
We use a Subscription Service to build webpages that people can visit to learn more about Xiris. Information that we collect and manage using the Subscription Service for our own marketing belongs to us and is used, disclosed and protected according to this Privacy Policy.
When You Visit our Websites
You are free to explore the Websites without providing any Personal Information about yourself. When you visit the Websites or register for the Subscription Service, we request that you provide Personal Information about yourself, and we collect Navigational Information.
Personal Information
This refers to any information that you voluntarily submit to us and that identifies you personally, including contact information, such as your name, e-mail address, company name, address, phone number, and other information about yourself or your business. Personal Information can also include information about any transactions, both free and paid, that you enter into on the Websites, and information about you that is available on the internet, such as from Facebook, LinkedIn, Twitter and Google, or information that we acquire from service providers.
Navigational Information
Personal Information includes Navigational Information where such information can directly or indirectly identify an individual. Navigational information refers to information about your computer and your visits to the Websites such as your IP address, geographical location, browser type, referral source, length of visit and pages viewed. Please see the “Use of Navigation Information” section below.
Log Files
When you view content provided by us, we automatically collect information about your computer hardware and software. This information can include your IP address, browser type, domain names, internet service provider (ISP), the files viewed on our site (e.g., HTML pages, graphics, etc.), operating system, clickstream data, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used by Xiris to provide general statistics regarding use of the Websites. For these purposes, we do link this automatically-collected data to other Personal Information such as name, email address, address, and phone number.
Information We Collect from Third Parties
From time to time, we may receive Personal Information about you from third party sources including partners with which we offer co-branded services or engage in joint marketing activities, and sources such as social media websites.
Information About Children\
The Websites are not intended for or targeted at children under 16, and we do not knowingly or intentionally collect personal information about children under 16 If you believe that we have collected personal information about a child under 16, please contact us at sales@xiris.com, so that we may delete the information.
How We Use Information We Collect
Compliance with Our Privacy Policy
We use the information we collect only in compliance with this Privacy Policy. Customers who subscribe to our Subscription Services are obligated through our agreements with them to comply with this Privacy Policy.
Selling Personal Information
We will never sell your Personal Information to any third party.
Use of Personal Information
In addition to the uses identified elsewhere in this Privacy Policy, we may use your Personal Information to:
Improve your browsing experience by personalizing the Websites and to improve the Subscription Service
Send information or Xiris content to you which we think may be of interest to you by post, email, or other means and send you marketing communications relating to our business
Promote use of our services to you and share promotional and information content with you in accordance with your communication preferences
Contact you about billing, account management, warranties and other administrative matters
Send information to you regarding changes to our Customer Terms of Service, Privacy Policy (including the Cookie Policy), or other legal agreements
Investigate and help prevent security issues and abuse
Meet legal requirements
We may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, we do not transfer your Personal Information to the third party.
Legal basis for processing Personal Information (EEA visitors only)
Our legal basis for collecting and using the personal information described above will depend on the personal information concerned and the specific context in which we collect it. However, we will normally collect personal information from you only where we have your consent to do so, where we need the personal information to perform a contract with you, or where the processing is in our legitimate interests and not overridden by your data protection interests or fundamental rights and freedoms. In some cases, we may also have a legal obligation to collect personal information from you.
If we ask you to provide personal information to comply with a legal requirement or to perform a contract with you, we will make this clear at the relevant time and advise you whether the provision of your personal information is mandatory or not (as well as of the possible consequences if you do not provide your personal information). Similarly, if we collect and use your personal information in reliance on our legitimate interests (or those of any third party), we will make clear to you at the relevant time what those legitimate interests are.
Use of Navigational Information
We use Navigational Information to operate and improve the Websites and to provide you with a better experience when you interact with Xiris. We may also use Navigational Information alone or in combination with Personal Information to provide you with personalized information about Xiris. Navigational Information, such as IP address, is used to approximate your location. For example, we may use your approximate location to provide content that has been translated or send emails at certain times using your local time zone.
You may disable the collection and use of your location data through browser-, operating system- or device-level settings. If you have any questions about consent concerning location data, please write to us by email at sales@xiris.com or by mail to Xiris Automation Inc., 1016 Sutton Drive, Unit C5, Burlington, Ontario, Canada L7L 6B8. Attn: Privacy.
Customer Testimonials and Comments
We post customer testimonials and comments on our Websites, which may contain Personal Information. We obtain each customer’s consent via email prior to posting the customer’s name and testimonial.
Security of your Personal Information
We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your Personal Information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. We secure the Personal Information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. All Personal Information is protected using appropriate physical, technical and organizational measures.For more on Security at Xiris, please write to us by email at sales@xiris.com or by mail to Xiris Automation Inc., 1016 Sutton Drive, Unit C5, Burlington, Ontario, Canada L7L 6B8. Attn: Privacy.
Social Media Features
Our Websites include Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button and Widgets, such as the Share Button or interactive mini-programs that run on our sites. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our sites, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Websites. This Privacy Policy does not apply to these features. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy and other policies of the companies providing them.
External Websites
Our Websites provide links to other websites of third parties. We do not control, and are not responsible for, the content or practices of these other websites. Our provision of such links does not constitute our endorsement of these other websites, their content, their owners, or their practices. This Privacy Policy does not apply to these other websites, which are subject to any privacy and other policies they may have.
Public Forums
We offer publicly accessible message boards, blogs, and community forums. Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose any information through our public message boards, blogs, or forums, this information may be collected and used by others. We will correct or delete any information you have posted on the Websites if you so request, as described in “To Unsubscribe From Our Communications” below.
Retention of Personal Information
How long we keep information we collect about you depends on the type of information, as described in further detail below. After such time, we will either delete or anonymize your information or, if this is not possible, then we will securely store your information and isolate it from any further use until deletion is possible.
We retain Personal Information that you provide to us where we have an ongoing legitimate business need to do so (for example, as needed to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements).
When we have no ongoing legitimate business need to process your Personal Information, we securely delete the information or anonymise it or, if this is not possible, securely store your Personal Information and isolate it from any further processing until deletion is possible. We will delete this information at an earlier date if you so request, as described in the “How to Access & Control Your Personal Data” below.
If you have elected to receive marketing communications from us, we retain information about your marketing preferences for a reasonable period of time from the date you last expressed interest in our content, products, or services, such as when you last opened an email from us or ceased using your Xiris account. We retain information derived from cookies and other tracking technologies for a reasonable period of time from the date such information was created. The data our customers collect by using the Subscription Service is retained according to the relevant agreements with our customers.
How We Share Information We Collect
Service Providers
We employ other third-party service providers to provide services on our behalf to visitors to our Websites and our customers and users of the Subscription Service and may need to share your information with them to provide information, products or services to you. Examples may include removing repetitive information from prospect lists, analyzing data or performing statistical analysis, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments, supplementing the information you provide us in order to provide you with better service, and providing customer service or support. These service providers are prohibited from using your Personal Information except for these purposes, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information. In all cases where we share your information with such agents, we explicitly require the agent to acknowledge and adhere to our privacy and customer data handling policies.
Xiris Partners (affiliates, dealers/retailers, and service suppliers)
In addition, we may share data with trusted partners to contact you based on your request to receive such communications, help us perform statistical analysis, or provide customer support. Such third parties are prohibited from using your Personal Information except for these purposes, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
We partner with trusted third parties to provide you with content that we think may be relevant to you. When you engage with these partners, we will tell you who we are sharing data with, and provide a link to the partner’s privacy policy so you can learn more about how to opt-out of the partner’s communications. These partners are required to adhere to our privacy and data protection policies. For more information on our partners or if you do not want us to share your personal information with these companies, please write to us by email at sales@xiris.com or by mail to Xiris Automation Inc., 1016 Sutton Drive, Unit C5, Burlington, Ontario, Canada L7L 6B8. Attn: Privacy.
Compelled Disclosure
We reserve the right to use or disclose your Personal Information if required by law or if we reasonably believe that use or disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or comply with a law, court order, or legal process.
Cookies
Xiris and our partners use cookies or similar technologies (such as JavaScript) to analyze trends, administer the website, track users’ movements around the website, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.
How to Access & Control Your Personal Data
Reviewing, Correcting and Removing Your Personal Information
You have the following data protection rights:
You can request access, correction, updates or deletion of your personal information.
You can object to processing of your personal information, ask us to restrict processing of your personal information or request portability of your personal information.
If we have collected and processed your personal information with your consent, then you can withdraw your consent at any time. Withdrawing your consent will not affect the lawfulness of any processing we conducted prior to your withdrawal, nor will it affect processing of your personal information conducted in reliance on lawful processing grounds other than consent.
You have the right to complain to a data protection authority about our collection and use of your personal information.
To exercise any of these rights, please write to us by email at sales@xiris.com or by mail to Xiris Automation Inc., 1016 Sutton Drive, Unit C5, Burlington, Ontario, Canada L7L 6B8. Attn: Privacy. We will respond to your request to change, correct, or delete your information within a reasonable time frame and notify you of the action we have taken.
To Unsubscribe From Our Communications
You may unsubscribe from our marketing communications by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link located on the bottom of our e-mails, updating your communication preferences, or by writing to us by email at sales@xiris.com or by mail to Xiris Automation Inc., 1016 Sutton Drive, Unit C5, Burlington, Ontario, Canada L7L 6B8. Attn: Privacy. Customers cannot opt out of receiving transactional emails related to their account with us or the Subscription Service.
How We Collect, Use, and Share your Personal Information
We have collected the following statutory categories of Personal Information in the past twelve (12) months:
Identifiers, such as name, e-mail address, mailing address, and phone number. We collect this information directly from you or from third party sources.
Commercial information, such as company records of products or services purchased, obtained or considered. We collect this information directly from you.
Internet or network information, such as browsing and search history. We collect this information directly from your device.
Geolocation data, such as IP address. We collect this information from your device.
Other personal information, in instances when you interact with us online, by phone or mail in the context of receiving help through our help desks or other support channels; participation in customer surveys or contests; or in providing products.
The business and commercial purposes for which we collect this information are described in Section 2 of this Privacy Policy. The categories of third parties to whom we “disclose” this information for a business purpose are described in Section 3 of this Privacy Policy.
Please contact us by email at sales@xiris.com or by mail to Xiris Automation Inc., 1016 Sutton Drive, Unit C5, Burlington, Ontario, Canada L7L 6B8, Attn: Privacy., if you:
Have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our privacy practices.
Need to access this policy in an alternative format.
Want to learn more about your rights or our privacy practices.
Need to designate an authorized agent to make a request on your behalf.
We periodically update this Privacy Policy. We will post any privacy policy changes on this page. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy periodically. We will also keep prior versions of this Privacy Policy in an archive for your review.
About
Our Team
Careers
Products
XVC-700 / 710
XVC-1000 / 1100
XVC-1000e / 1100e
XVC-S
Translate »
